frameiteasy.com 2017-08-09

# Privacy - Frame It Easy

Privacy Policy

FrameItEasy.com, respects the privacy of our customers.  
Any and all information collected through our system is treated with the utmost care.

* * *

FrameItEasy.com's Privacy Guarantee

FrameItEasy.com asks customers to supply various personal data when placing an order, such as name and address, credit-card information, and E-mail address. We use this data only for the purpose of filling an order, or communicating with the customer or supplier about the status of an order.

We will release personally identifiable information to third parties and organizations when we believe it is appropriate for us to do so in order to comply with the law or to protect against fraud. We will also release such information to cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental investigations (without necessarily requiring the requesting law enforcement or government agency to formally serve us with a subpoena), comply with all valid court orders or subpoenas, protect the legal rights of us and our users, or when we believe it is needed for fraud protection and/or credit risk reduction.

Except for the circumstances set forth in the previous paragraph, we will not knowingly distribute customer information to be used in mailing lists, surveys, or any other purpose other than what is required to perform our services.

* * *

What information do we collect? How do we use it?

When ordering from any of our partner sites, FrameItEasy.com must collect the purchaser's name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill orders and provide notification of the order status.

* * *

How does FrameItEasy.com protect customer information?

Customers who buy through the FrameItEasy.com system are shopping on a secure server, which encrypts all of the customer's personal information including name, address and credit card number. Encryption ensures that no one can access or use personal information in an unauthorized manner.

FrameItEasy.com has made an investment in protecting our clients' and customers' information utilizing the following technologies:

**SSL (Secure Socket Layers)**

Because we accept sensitive information from end-users such as passwords and credit card numbers, FrameItEasy.com's site uses SSL. This logic encrypts the data being sent to the server from the browser using high-level encryption technology. Once the data is received from customers on the FrameItEasy.com Network, it may be required that the data be maintained for a certain period of time inside our private network. Encrypting the data means it cannot be viewed in plain text. 

* * *

What about cookies?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. FrameItEasy.com's cookies are used only to identify the customer, not to identify any specific customer traits. These cookies do not store sensitive data. This enables a more pleasant shopping experience with FrameItEasy.com every time you shop with us.

* * *
